{"data":[{"question":"The teacher repeated the assignment again for the students, since they had difficulty understanding what to do after he had explained it the first time.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"again","c":"since they","d":"had explained","answer":"2","explain":" - Again-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The company has little money that it can't hardly operate anymore.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"little","c":"that it","d":"can't hardly","answer":"2","explain":" - Little-> so little","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The professor is thinking to go to the conference on environment next month.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"to go","c":"on environment","d":"next month","answer":"2","explain":" - To go-> of going","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The statement will be spoken just one time; therefore, you must listen very careful in order to understand what the speaker has said.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"will be spoken","b":"must listen","c":"careful","d":"has said","answer":"3","explain":" - Careful-> carefully","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The pilot agreed to land the plane only when the hijackers threatened to shoot some of the passenger.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to land","b":"only","c":"to shoot","d":"passenger","answer":"4","explain":" - Passenger-> passengers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Someone was showed the child how to use the telephone.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was showed","b":"the child","c":"to use","d":"the","answer":"1","explain":" - Was showed-> showed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"The search party had idea little where start looking.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"idea little","c":"start","d":"looking","answer":"2","explain":" - Idea little-> little idea","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Police have to break the meeting up yesterday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have to","b":"break","c":"the","d":"up","answer":"1","explain":" - Have to-> had to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"We are suppose to read all of chapter seven and answer the question for tomorrow's class.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"suppose","b":"all of chapter","c":"answer","d":"for tomorrow's class","answer":"1","explain":" - Suppose> supposed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Because the committee was anxious to attend the celebration, the president dispensed to reading the minutes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because the committee was anxious","b":"the","c":"to reading","d":"minutes","answer":"3","explain":" - To reading-> to read","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}